Shadows lengthen on the wall The sequence has
begun A chill is blowing through the hall
Awakening the sun We read the signs in broken
glass And traced the hidden lines Another empty
day will pass Another fate declines Your games
are turning in the dark Above the factory floor
We try to catch the fadding spark Behind the
heavy dark Can you see the prophecy unfold? It's
unfolding Shadows in the stories we were told
A prophecy unfolds
A thousand voices in the wire A whisper in the
screen We feed the papers to the fire To keep the
engine clean You lock the gate and turn the key
You try to understand How anything was meant to
be Inside this hololand Just to remain against
the tide Against the bitter cold With nowhere
left for us to hide Exactly as foretold Can you
see the prophecy unfold? It's unfolding
Shadows in stories we were told
I turn the wheel and watch the cold hours run
Hitting from the freezing of the sun A prophecy
unfolds
Is Irion in the code? At the ending of the road We
are running out of time. We are running out of
time.
Can you see? The prophecy unfolds It's
unfolding Shadows In the stories we were told
Turn the wheel and watch the cold clouds run
Hidden from the freezing of the sun A prophecy
unfolds
It's unfolding